Congratulations to all surviving
passengers on clearing the level.
First stop, the Nether Mortuary.
Instance difficulty has increased.
All remaining points will be automatically
converted into initial advantages.
Points requirement met.
Exclusive skill "Forensic Investigation"
upgraded successfully.
Looks like brains really do beat brawn
in this hellhole.
Judging by the mess outside,
the next level will be even tougher.
How about we keep teaming up?
You find the clues,
and I'll do the fighting.
Teaming up is fine,
but let me be clear.
Put away your sympathy.
In this hellhole,
the bleeding hearts die first.
Don't worry.
My life is valuable too.
We're here.
Welcome to the Ghost Empress's
Deep Palace.
Main quest for this stop:
At midnight, during the Ancestral
Sacrifice Ceremony,
assassinate the pinnacle of power
to appease the resentment
of the deep palace
and break the deadlock.
The palace? Assassinate the pinnacle
of power?
Are they asking us to kill the emperor?
Welcoming the Head of the
Imperial Hospital.
Lower officials, step back three paces.
Do not look directly at the
Head Physician.
Instance environment change detected.
Player weapons have been localized.
He's with me.
The knife.
Put it away.
Why do you guys get to dress so well?
Why am I wearing a sack?
This stupid game is targeting me.
You mannerless lowly eunuch!
The cut from the castration room
still hurts, doesn't it?
Imperial Physician Xiao is the
Empress Dowager's favorite.
If you offend him,
how many layers of skin do you
have to be flayed?
Get over here and kowtow right now!
I-I won't kowtow.
Why the hell should I kowtow to him?
I'll kowtow.
Xiao Han ranked first in points
last round.
Chen Qiang was at the bottom
with zero points.
So in this instance,
points determine your starting class
and fate.
Hand it over. The Empress Dowager
has ordered
that such unlucky things like yellow paper
and cinnabar are forbidden in the palace.
Eunuch, it's just an ordinary
peace amulet.
There's no need for this.
Imperial Physician Xiao,
you are a smart man.
The late emperor just passed away,
and the little prince is still young.
In this deep palace,
the Empress Dowager's decree
is the law of heaven.
The wrath of heaven cannot be defied.
Leave me alone.
This stupid game...
what does it matter even if we clear it?
Don't be afraid.
I'm coming to join you.
The Empress Dowager decrees:
Summon Imperial Physician Xiao
for an audience.
Human lives are treated like dirt.
It seems in this man-eating palace,
the Empress Dowager is the absolute
pinnacle of power.
The Empress Dowager only summoned me.
Why are you following me?
Hmph, don't flatter yourself.
This Empress Dowager is probably the
"pinnacle of power" the system mentioned.
I need to keep an eye on things,
lest someone dies without knowing how
just to hog all the points.
Her Grace's bedchamber is restricted.
No men allowed.
What if I insist?
If I'm not out by the midnight bell,
do as you see fit.
Fine.
If you're not out
past midnight,
I'll level this Kunning Palace.
Remember, don't die an ugly death.
I don't want to go in
and fish out a rotten corpse.
Dr. Xiao, do you smell it?
The wind in the palace has changed.
There's a new stench of death.
Come check on the royal heir.
If you can't cure him, you'll end up
like that cold corpse outside.
is your end.
Since she's already at the peak of power,
why bother testing me?
Summoning me alone late at night,
what is she after?
Missing dominant genetic traits.
This isn't royal blood at all.
No reaction to pain.
He's been fed nerve-paralyzing drugs
for a long time.
This child is a scapegoat
who could die at any moment.
To Your Grace, the royal heir is fine.
Dr. Xiao,
wait for me a moment.
Lowly slave,
worse than a dog.
How dare you slack off
when told to scrub the chamber pots?
I think you have a death wish.
Trash. Slack off again
and you'll be thrown into the mass grave.
I will climb up
and trample all of you under my feet.
Lin Xiaofei, are you blind?
Can't you see your boss suffering here?
Hurry up and scrub these pots for me.
Sister Lin, it smells awful. Let's go.
You've got some nerve, haven't you?
How dare you talk back to me?
Believe it or not, once we clear this
and return to the company,
I'll fire you immediately.
I'll make sure you can never work
in this industry again.
Mr. Chen, this isn't the company.
If you still can't face reality,
scrub the pots yourself.
Qiqi, let's go.
Hurry.
Bitch.
Just you wait.
Peak of power, huh?
As long as I kill the Empress Dowager,
the clearance points are mine.
When we get to the next instance,
I'll be the rules.
I'll trample you all to death, one by one.